<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<xliff xmlns="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.2" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2 xliff-core-1.2-transitional.xsd">
  <file datatype="xml" original="ns-System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement.xml" source-language="en-US" target-language="ru-RU">
    <header>
      <tool tool-id="mdxliff" tool-name="mdxliff" tool-version="1.0-efd8310" tool-company="Microsoft" />
      <xliffext:skl_file_name xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">5a83ea4b-dd12-480b-bfc8-267272ef1864fefc91ccc5056e6a3e0640141b2ea2b1dffd83da.skl</xliffext:skl_file_name>
      <xliffext:version xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">1.2</xliffext:version>
      <xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">fefc91ccc5056e6a3e0640141b2ea2b1dffd83da</xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash>
      <xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">df6cf590aa3087f6c7c202712eee781c6a3c8f96</xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit>
      <xliffext:ms.lasthandoff xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">05/10/2018</xliffext:ms.lasthandoff>
    </header>
    <body>
      <group id="content" extype="content">
        <trans-unit id="101" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve">
          <source>The <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /&gt;</ph> namespace provides uniform access and manipulation of user, computer, and group security principals across the multiple principal stores: Active Directory Domain Services (AD DS), Active Directory Lightweight Directory Services (AD LDS), and Machine SAM (MSAM).</source>
          <target state="translated">Пространство имен <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /&gt;</ph> обеспечивает унифицированный доступ и управление такими участниками безопасности, как пользователь, компьютер и группа, находящимися в различных хранилищах участников: доменных службах Active Directory (AD DS), службах Active Directory облегченного доступа к каталогам (AD LDS) и диспетчере учетных записей безопасности компьютера (MSAM).</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="102" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve">
          <source><ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /&gt;</ph> manages directory objects independent of the <ph id="ph2">&lt;see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices" /&gt;</ph> namespace.</source>
          <target state="translated"><ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /&gt;</ph> управляет объектами каталога независимо от пространства имен <ph id="ph2">&lt;see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices" /&gt;</ph>.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="103" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Managed directory services applications can take advantage of the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement&gt;</ph> API to simplify management of user, computer and group principals.</source>
          <target state="translated">Каталог управляемых приложений служб можно воспользоваться преимуществами <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement&gt;</ph> API для упрощения управления субъектов-пользователей, компьютеров и группы.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="104" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Solutions that previously required intricate knowledge of the store or lengthy code, such as finding all groups to which a user belongs, are accomplished in a few lines of code with the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement&gt;</ph> API.</source>
          <target state="translated">Решения, которые раньше требовали сложных знаний хранилища или большой фрагмент кода, например, для поиска всех групп, к которым принадлежит пользователь, выполняется в несколько строк кода, <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement&gt;</ph> API.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="105" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>The following features are available on the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement&gt;</ph> API:</source>
          <target state="translated">Следующие функции, доступные на <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement&gt;</ph> API:</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="106" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Basic directory operations such as creating and updating security principals is simplified.</source>
          <target state="translated">Основные операции с каталогами, таких как создание и обновление субъектов безопасности упрощается.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="107" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>The application requires less knowledge of the underlying stores to perform these operations.</source>
          <target state="translated">Приложению требуется меньше информации мест хранения для выполнения этих операций.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="108" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Applications can extend the object model to include new types of directory objects.</source>
          <target state="translated">Приложения могут расширять объектную модель, добавляя новые типы объектов каталога.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="109" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Account management tasks, such as enabling and disabling a user account, are simplified.</source>
          <target state="translated">Упрощены задачи управления учетными записями, такие как включение и отключение учетной записи пользователя.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="110" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Cross-store support allows group objects in the Active Directory Domain Services (AD DS), Active Directory Lightweight Directory Services (AD LDS), and Machine SAM (MSAM) databases to contain members from different types of stores.</source>
          <target state="translated">Поддержка разных хранилищ позволяет объектам-группам в доменных служб Active Directory (AD DS), службы Active Directory облегченного доступа к каталогам (AD LDS) и базы данных SAM компьютера (MSAM) содержать элементы из различных типов хранилищ.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="111" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Query by example searching, available on the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement.PrincipalSearcher&gt;</ph> class, enables applications to set properties on a principal object and search the selected store for other objects that contain matching property values.</source>
          <target state="translated">Запрос, выполняя поиск пример, доступных на <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement.PrincipalSearcher&gt;</ph> класса приложениям позволяет задать свойства для объекта principal и искать в выбранном хранилище для других объектов, содержащих совпадающие значения свойств.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="112" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Enhanced search on computer, user and group principal objects enables applications to search the selected store for matching principal objects.</source>
          <target state="translated">Улучшенный поиск на компьютере, пользователь и группа позволяет приложениям искать в выбранном хранилище соответствующие объекты-участники.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="113" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Recursive search, available on the group principal object, enables applications to search a group recursively and return only principal objects that are leaf nodes.</source>
          <target state="translated">Рекурсивный поиск объекта-участника группы, позволяет приложениям искать группу рекурсивно и возвращать только основной объекты, которые являются листовыми узлами.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="114" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Credential validation against the Machine SAM, AD DS, and AD LS stores is simplified.</source>
          <target state="translated">Проверка учетных данных на хранилищах SAM компьютера AD DS и AD LS упрощено.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="115" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Connections speeds are increased by using the Fast Concurrent Bind (FSB) feature when available.</source>
          <target state="translated">С помощью функции быстрого параллельных привязки (частота) при наличии увеличены скорости подключений.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="116" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Connection caching decreases the number of ports used.</source>
          <target state="translated">Кэширование подключения уменьшает число используемых портов.</target>       </trans-unit>
      </group>
    </body>
  </file>
</xliff>